Guide to the Bella Abzug papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series V: Subject Files
  - Subseries V.37: Nixon, Richard Milhous
    - Messages, Statements, Press Releases (Box 496)
    - Papers (Box 496)
    - Pension and Expenses, Post-Resignation (Box 496)
    - San Clemente and other Properties--General; Lawsuits (Louis Stokes et al.) (Box 496)
    - Saxbe, William--Appointment (Box 497)
    - Subpoena (Box 497)
    - Taxes (Box 497)
    - Watergate:
      - General (Box 497)
      - Hearings and Testimony (Box 497)
      - Legislation
        - Special Prosecutor--General; Lawsuit (Ralph Nader vs. Robert Bork) (Box 497)
        - Watergate: (Box 498)
      - Tapes:
        - General (Box 498)
        - Lawsuits (Box 498)
        - Transcripts and Auditing Schedules (Box 498)
      - Printed (Box 498)
      - Printed (Box 498)
  - Subseries V.38: Peace Movement
    - Correspondence (Box 499)
    - Americans for Democratic Action (Box 499)
    - Another Mother for Peace (Box 499)
    - Barnstorming Tours (Box 499)
    - Berrigan Case (Box 499)
    - Center for Defense Information (Box 499)
    - Citizens of Conscience (Box 499)
    - Coalition for Human Needs and Budget Priorities (Box 499)
    - Coalition to stop Funding the War (Box 499)
    - Continental Walk (Box 499)
    - Friends Committee on National Legislation (Box 499)
    - Indochina Resource Center (Box 500)
    - Kennedy, Jane--Nobel Prize (Box 500)
    - League of Women Voters (Box 500)
    - Lower East Side Mobi1ization for Peace Action (LEMPA) (Box 500)
    - Members of Congress for Peace Through Law, (2 Folders) (Box 500)
    - National Peace Action Coalition (Box 501)
    - Organizations--Miscellaneous (Box 501)
    - SANE (Box 501)
    - Tiger Cage Project (Box 501)
    - Vietnam Veterans Against the War (Box 501)
    - Washington Peace Center (Box 501)
    - Women Strike for Peace (Box 501)
    - Women Strike for Peace--Survival Campaign (Box 501)
    - Women Volunteers to Vietnam (Box 501)
    - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom (Box 501)
    - World Peace Tax Fund (Box 501)
  - Subseries V.39: Political Affairs
    - Correspondence (Box 502)
    - Abzug--Notes; Memoranda; Statements and Activities (Box 502)
    - General (Box 502)
    - Campaigns and Candidates:
      - General (Box 502)
      - 1973 (Box 502)
      - 1974, (2 Folders) (Box 503)
      - 1976 (Box 503)
      - Badillo, Herman (Box 503)
      - Blumenthal, Albert H. (Box 504)
      - Carter, Jimmy (Box 504)
      - Farbstein, Leonard (Box 504)
      - Goldberg, Arthur (Box 504)
      - Krupsak, Mary Anne (Box 504)
      - McGovern, George, and Sargent Shriver (and Thomas Eagleton) (Box 504)
      - Tuite, Dan (Box 504)
      - Udall, Morris (Box 505)
      - Weiss, Ted (Box 505)
    - Democratic Caucus, U.S. Congress (Box 505)
    - Democratic National Committee:
      - General (Box 505)
      - Issue Papers, 1974 (Box 505)
      - Publications and Releases (Box 505)
    - Democratic Party--Correspondence (Box 505)
    - Democratic Party: (Box 506)
      - General (Box 506)
      - Affirmative Action (Box 506)
      - Conference, 1974 (Kansas City) (Box 506)
      - National Convention and Platform, 1972 (Box 506)
      - New York State Women's Mini-Convention (Box 506)
      - Platform, 1976
        - General (Box 506)
        - Draft (notebook) (Box 507)
        - Drafts, Notes and Amendments (Box 507)
        - Regional Hearing Summaries (Box 507)
        - Speaker's Task Force Report (Box 507)
        - Testimony and Presentations, (3 Folders) (Box 508)
        - Clippings (Box 508)
    - Election Boards (Box 509)
    - Electoral Vote (Box 509)
    - Endorsements, (2 Folders) (Box 509)
    - Legislation--92nd Congress (Box 509)
    - Legislation: (Box 510)
      - 93rd Congress:
        - General (Box 510)
        - Voter Registration by Mail (Box 510)
        - HR 16090 (Federal Election Campaigns) (Box 510)
      - 94th Congress:
        - Federal Election Commission and Federal Election Law, (2 Folders) (Box 510)
        - HR 8617 (Federal Employees in Campaigns) (Box 510)
        - Voter Registration by Mail (Box 510)
    - Liberal Party (Box 511)
    - National Caucus of Labor Committees (Box 511)
    - New Democratic Coalition:
      - Correspondence and Memoranda (Box 511)
      - General (Box 511)
      - Meetings and Conventions (Box 511)
      - Publications and Printed Material (Box 511)
    - New York State Democratic Committee, 1971-1976 and n.d. (Box 512)
    - Organizations:
      - General (Box 512)
      - Americans for Democratic Action (Box 513)
      - Black Caucus, U.S. Congress (Box 513)
      - Common Cause--Correspondence; General (Box 513)
      - National Women's Political Caucus (Box 513)
      - Student Vote (Box 513)
    - Organizations, Democratic: (Box 514)
      - General Bolivar (Box 514)
      - Douglass Democratic Club (Box 514)
      - Roosevelt Independent Democrats (Box 514)
      - Village Independent Democrats (Box 514)
    - Priorities, National (Box 514)
    - State Constitutions and Conventions (Box 514)
    - Sutton, Percy E.--Political Seminar (Box 514)
    - U. S. Labor Party (Box 514)
    - Voting (Box 514)
    - Women (Box 514)
    - Printed (Box 514)
  - Subseries V.40: Postal Service, U.S.
    - Correspondence, 1970-1976 (Box 515)
    - Abzug--Notes and Memoranda (Box 515)
    - General (Box 516)
    - Hearing, 13 July 1971 (Box 516)
    - Legislation (Box 516)
    - Postal Academy (Box 516)
    - Stamps (Box 516)
    - Unions (Box 516)
  - Subseries V.41: Presidency, U.S.
    - Correspondence (Box 517)
    - Abzug--Statements, Notes and Memoranda (Box 517)
    - General (Box 517)
    - Election, Special (Box 517)
    - Emergency, National (Box 517)
    - Expenditures (Box 517)
    - Impoundment (Box 517)
    - Privilege, Executive (Box 518)
    - Succession, Presidential and Vice-Presidential (Box 518)
    - War Powers:
      - Abzug--Statements, Notes and Memoranda (Box 518)
      - Legislation (Box 518)
      - Printed (Box 518)
  - Subseries V.42: Public Works
    - Correspondence (Box 519)
    - Abzug--Notes, Memoranda and Statements (Box 519)
    - General (Box 519)
    - Albany (N.Y.) Waterfront (Box 519)
    - Army (U.S.) Corps of Engineers (Box 519)
    - Committee on Public Works, U.S. House of Representatives--General (Box 519)
    - Committee on Public Works, U.S. House of Representatives-- Meetings, Hearings and Testimony (Box 520)
    - Deepwater Ports (Box 520)
    - Economic Development:
      - Correspondence (Box 520)
      - Abzug--Notes, Memoranda and Statements (Box 520)
      - General (Box 520)
      - Economic Development Administration Reports (Box 521)
      - Legislation:
        - General and 92nd Congress (Box 521)
        - 93rd Congress (Box 521)
        - 94th Congress--Abzug--Notes, Memoranda and Statements (Box 521)
        - 94th Congress: (Box 522)
          - General (Box 522)
          - Hearings and Testimony (Box 522)
          - HR 4074 (see also: OVERSIZE) (Box 522)
          - HR 5247 (Box 522)
          - Correspondence (Box 522)
          - Abzug--Notes, Memos, Statements (Box 522)
          - General (see also OVERSIZE) (Box 522)
          - Hearings and Testimony (Box 522)
          - HR 9398 (Box 523)
          - Public Works and Economic Development Act of 1965- Amendments (Box 523)
          - Public Works Employment Act of 1976 (PL94-369) (Box 523)
          - Senate--General; S 1587 (Box 523)
      - New York City and State (Box 523)
      - New York City--Lower East Side (Box 523)
      - Printed (Box 523)
    - Gowanus Dredging (Box 524)
    - Great Lakes and St. Lawrence Seaway (Box 524)
    - Greenburgh (N.Y.) Flood Control (Box 524)
    - Hudson River Maintenance and Dredging (Box 524)
    - Legislation--General (Box 524)
    - New York City--Harbor Drift: (Box 524)
    - Correspondence (Box 524)
    - Abzug--Notes and Memoranda (Box 524)
    - General, (2 Folders) (Box 525)
    - Legislation (Box 525)
    - New York City--Piers (Box 525)
    - New York City, State and Region--Water Projects, Miscellaneous (Box 525)
    - New York State Water Pollution Reimbursement: (Box 526)
      - Correspondence, Notes, Memos and Statements (Box 526)
      - General (Box 526)
    - Parks: (Box 526)
    - General (Box 526)
    - New York City and State (Box 526)
    - Public Buildings and Grounds--Correspondence, Notes and Memoranda (Box 526)
    - Public Buildings and Grounds: (Box 527)
      - General (Box 527)
      - Hearings and Reports (Box 527)
    - Rockaway and Coney Island, N.Y. (Box 527)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority Pollution Control Credits (Box 527)
    - Tocks Island Dam Project (Box 527)
    - Water Pollution:
      - Correspondence (Box 527)
      - Abzug--Notes, Memoranda and Statements (Box 527)
      - General (Box 527)
      - Hearings, February 1974 (Box 528)
      - Hearings and Statements, Miscellaneous (Box 528)
      - Legislation--General; 94th Congress--HR 9650 (Box 528)
    - Water Resources: (Box 529)
      - General (Box 529)
      - Legislation, 1976 (Box 529)
      - Port Authority of New York and New Jersey (Box 529)
      - Watershed Projects (Box 529)
    - Printed (Box 529)
  - Subseries V.43: Religion
    - Correspondence (Box 530)
    - General (Box 530)
    - Network (Box 530)
  - Subseries V.44: Revenue Sharing
    - Correspondence (Box 530)
    - Abzug--Notes, Memoranda and Statements General (Box 530)
    - Hearings and Testimony (Box 530)
    - Legislation (Box 531)
    - National Clearinghouse on Revenue Sharing (Box 531)
    - New York City and state Reports (Box 531)
    - Treasury, U.S. Department of--Office of Revenue Sharing (Box 531)
    - Printed (Box 531)
  - Subseries V.45: Rockefeller, Nelson A.
    - Correspondence, (4 Folders) (Box 532)
    - Abzug: (Box 533)
      - Notes and Memoranda (Box 533)
      - Statements, Releases and Drafts of Correspondence (Box 533)
    - General (Box 533)
    - Finances (Box 533)
    - Hearings and Testimony (Box 533)
    - Legislation (Box 534)
    - Memorandum of Law (Box 534)
    - Ronan, William J.--Finances (Box 534)
    - Printed (Box 534)
  - Subseries V.46: Science
    - Correspondence (Box 534)
    - General (Box 534)
    - Space Shuttle (Box 534)
  - Subseries V.47: Social Security
    - Correspondence, 1970-1974 (Box 535)
    - Correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box 536)
    - Abzug--Notes, Memoranda and Statements (Box 536)
    - General (Box 537)
    - Hearings and Testimony, 1973-1976 (Box 537)
    - Legislation: (Box 538)
      - By Abzug:
        - 92nd Congress (Box 538)
        - 93rd Congress, (2 Folders) (Box 538)
        - 94th Congress (Box 538)
      - General (Box 538)
      - 92nd Congress (Box 539)
      - 93rd Congress (Box 539)
      - 94th Congress (Box 539)
    - National Association of Manufacturers Meeting, 14 April 1975 (Box 539)
    - New York City and State (Box 539)
    - Reports (Box 539)
    - Social Security Administration--General; Program Circulars (Box 540)
    - Supplemental Security Income--Correspondence, 1974 and n.d. (Box 540)
    - Supplemental Security Income: (Box 541)
      - Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 541)
      - Abzug:
        - Memoranda (Box 541)
        - Notes (Box 541)
        - Releases (Box 541)
        - Statements and Testimony (Box 541)
      - General (Box 542)
      - Claims Manual (Box 542)
      - Community Council of Greater New York (Box 542)
      - Emergency Action Committee on SSI (Box 542)
      - Hearings and Testimony (Box 542)
    - Legislation by Abzug: (Box 543)
      - General and 92nd Congress (Box 543)
      - 93rd Congress (Box 543)
      - 94th Congress (Box 543)
    - New York City and State (Box 543)
    - Reports and Handbooks (Box 544)
    - Printed (Box 544)
    - Title XX:
      - Correspondence, Notes, Memoranda and Statements (Box 544)
      - General (Box 544)
      - Health, Education and Welfare, U.S. Dept. of Conference, 26 June 1975 (Box 545)
      - Legislation (Box 545)
      - Means Test--Correspondence; General (Box 545)
      - New York City and State (Box 545)
    - Women--General (SEE ALSO: WOMEN--Social Security, Box 637) (Box 546)
    - Printed, (3 Folders) (Box 546)
  - Subseries V.48: Social Services
    - General (Box 547)
    - Disaster Relief (Box 547)
    - Family Courts (Box 547)
    - National Association of Social Workers (Box 547)
    - New York City: (Box 547)
    - General (Box 547)
    - Human Resources Administration (Box 547)
    - Organizations, Miscellaneous (Box 547)
    - Quaker Committee on Social Rehabilitation (Box 547)
    - Red Cross (Box 547)
    - VISTA (Box 547)
  - Subseries V.49: Taxes
    - Correspondence, 1971-1974 (Box 548)
    - Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 549)
    - Abzug--Notes, Memoranda, Statements and Activities (Box 549)
    - General (Box 549)
    - Handicapped (Box 549)
    - Internal Revenue Service (Box 550)
    - Legislation:
      - General (Box 550)
      - 92nd Congress (Box 550)
      - 93rd Congress (Box 550)
      - 94th Congress (Box 550)
    - New York City and State (Box 551)
    - Oil Industry (Box 551)
    - Property (Box 551)
    - Reform (Box 551)
    - Renters (Box 551)
    - Single Taxpayers (Box 551)
    - Tax Foundation (Box 551)
    - War Resistance (Box 551)
    - Printed (Box 551)
  - Subseries V.50: Transportation
    - Correspondence, 1970-1976 (Box 552)
    - Abzug--Memoranda and Notes; Statements and Releases (Box 553)
    - General, (2 Folders) (Box 553)
    - Automobiles (Box 554)
    - Aviation:
      - Correspondence (Box 554)
      - General (Box 554)
      - Federal Aviation Administration (Box 554)
      - Hijacking (Box 554)
      - Legislation (Box 554)
      - Pan American World Airways (Box 554)
      - STOLport (Box 554)
      - Supersonic Transport (SST): (Box 555)
      - Correspondence, 1970-1976 (Box 555)
      - SST:
        - Abzug--Notes, statements and memoranda (Box 555)
        - General (Box 555)
        - Hearings and Testimony (Box 556)
        - Lawsuits:
          - Environmental Defense Fund (Box 556)
          - New York State and Miscellaneous (Box 556)
        - Legislation (Box 556)
        - Organizations:
          - General (Box 556)
          - Environmental Defense Fund (Box 556)
          - Metro Suburban Aircraft Noise Association, Inc. (Box 556)
        - Reports (Box 557)
        - Printed (Box 557)
    - Elderly and Handicapped:
      - Correspondence (Box 557)
      - Abzug--Notes, Memoranda, Statements Releases and Activities (Box 557)
      - General (Box 557)
      - Legislation (Box 558)
      - New York City and State (Box 558)
      - Transportation, U.S. Department of-Regulations, Procedures and Applications (Box 558)
    - Hearings and Testimony--miscellaneous (Box 558)
    - Highways: (Box 559)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1976 (Box 559)
    - Abzug--Notes, memoranda, statements and Releases (Box 559)
    - General (Box 560)
    - Beautification (Box 560)
    - Hearings and Testimony, 1970-3/1973 (Box 560)
    - Hearings and Testimony, 3/1973, (3 Folders) (Box 561)
    - Hearings and Testimony, 1974-1976 (Box 562)
    - Highway Trust Fund (Box 562)
    - Highway Users Federation (Box 562)
    - Legislation:
      - To 1970 and n.d. (Box 562)
      - 92nd Congress (Box 562)
      - 93rd Congress--General (Box 562)
    - Legislation: (Box 563)
      - 93rd Congress:
        - HR 5573 (Abzug Bill) (Box 563)
        - Federal Aid Highways 1973 (Box 563)
        - (S502/HR 6288)--4 Folders SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 563)
      - 93rd Congress--Federal Aid Highways 1974 (Box 564)
      - 94th Congress:
        - General (Box 564)
        - Federal Aid Highways Act, 1975 (Box 564)
        - General (Box 564)
        - Abzug Interstate Transfer Amendment (Box 564)
    - New York City and State (Box 565)
    - Safety:
      - General (Box 565)
      - Center for Auto Safety--Report, 1975 (Box 565)
    - Transportation, U.S. Department of:
      - Newsletters (Box 565)
      - Publications and General Information (Box 565)
    - Printed (1) (Box 565)
    - Printed (2) (Box 566)
    - Legislation:
      - General and n.d. (Box 566)
      - 92nd Congress (Box 566)
      - 93rd Congress:
        - General (Box 566)
        - Unified Transportation Assistance Act (UTAP)--General (Box 566)
        - Unified Transportation Assistance Act (Box 567)
        - (UTAP)--Hearings, (2 Folders) (Box 567)
      - 94th Congress (Box 567)
    - Mass Transit: (Box 568)
      - Correspondence, 1970-1976 (Box 568)
      - Abzug--Notes, Memoranda, Statements and Releases (Box 568)
      - General (Box 568)
      - American Public Transit Association (American Transit Association) (Box 569)
      - Buses (Box 569)
      - Funding--General (Box 569)
      - Hearings and Testimony (Box 569)
      - Legislation:
        - Urban Mass Transportation Act of 1964 with miscellaneous amendments (Box 569)
        - 9lst--92nd Congresses, and n.d. (Box 569)
        - 93rd Congress--General (Box 569)
        - 93rd Congress: (Box 570)
          - Urban Mass Transportation Assistance Act of 1973 (Box 570)
          - Federal Mass Transportation Act of 1974 (Box 570)
        - 94th Congress (Box 570)
      - New York City and State (Box 570)
      - Reports (Box 571)
      - Transportation, U.S. Department of:
        - General (Box 571)
        - Urban Mass Transportation Administration (Box 571)
      - Printed (Box 571)
    - New York City: (Box 572)
      - Correspondence (Box 572)
      - Abzug--Notes, memoranda, releases and statements (Box 572)
      - General (Box 572)
      - Air Quality and Midtown Transportation Study (Box 572)
      - Bronzaft, Arline (Subway Study) (Box 572)
      - Committee for Better Transit (Box 572)
      - Manhattan--West Side (1 Folder, 1 volume) (Box 572)
      - Manhattan and Bronx Surface Transit Operating Authority (MABSFOA) (Box 573)
      - Manhattan Auto Study (Box 573)
      - Mass Transit:
        - General (Box 573)
        - Fares (Box 573)
        - Financing (Box 573)
        - Subways: (Box 574)
          - General (Box 574)
          - 72nd Street IRT Station (Box 574)
      - Parking Regulations and Facilities (Box 574)
      - Reports (Box 574)
      - Riverdale Buses (Box 574)
      - Taxis (Box 574)
      - Transit Authority (Box 574)
      - Transportation Administration (Box 574)
      - Westway: (Box 575)
        - Correspondence:
          - General (Box 575)
          - Form Letters, (2 Folders) (Box 575)
        - Abzug--Notes and Memoranda; Statements and Releases (Box 576)
        - General (Box 576)
        - Community Boards--General; COMBO (Box 576)
        - Environmental Protection Agency, U.S. (Box 576)
        - Gansevoort Meat Market (Box 577)
        - Hearings and Testimony (Box 577)
        - Legislation and U.S. Code (Box 577)
        - Meetings (Box 577)
        - Organizations (Box 577)
        - Reports (Box 577)
        - Reports (1 Folder, 13 volumes) (Box 578)
        - Reports (6 volumes; SEE ALSO OVERSIZE) (Box 579)
        - West Side Highway Project (Box 580)
        - Printed (Box 580)
    - New York State and Region:
      - Correspondence, Notes, Memoranda and Releases (Box 580)
      - General (Box 580)
      - Bond Issue, 1971-1973 (Box 580)
      - Buffalo, N.Y. (and Amherst Corridor) (Box 580)
      - Hearings and Testimony (Box 581)
      - Metropolitan Transportation Authority (Box 581)
      - Reports (Box 581)
      - Lawrence County (Box 581)
      - Select Legislative Committee on Transportation (Box 581)
      - Tolls, Bridge and Tunnel (Box 581)
      - Transportation, New York State Dept. of (Box 582)
      - Tri-State and Regional Planning Association (Box 582)
    - Ports and Waterways:
      - General (Box 582)
      - Lighterage (Box 582)
      - St. Lawrence Seaway (Box 582)
    - Railroads:
      - Correspondence and Memoranda (Box 582)
      - General and Notes (Box 582)
      - Amtrak (Box 583)
      - Hearings and Testimony Legislation (Box 583)
      - New York City, State and Region (Box 583)
      - Reports (Box 583)
      - U.S. Railway Association (Box 584)
      - Printed (Box 584)
    - Transportation, U.S. Department of--Publications (Box 584)
    - Trucking (Box 584)
    - Urban Transportation--General (Box 584)
    - Urban Transportation--Reports (Box 585)
    - Printed--Periodicals; Congressional Record; Miscellaneous, (2 Folders) (Box 585)
  - Subseries V.51: Urban Affairs
    - Correspondence (Box 586)
    - General (Box 586)
    - District of Columbia (Box 586)
    - Legislation (Box 586)
    - "National Cities" (Box 586)
    - Suburban Action Institute (Box 586)
  - Subseries V.52: Utilities
    - Correspondence (Box 586)
    - General (Box 586)
    - Consolidated Edison: (Box 586)
    - General (Box 586)
    - Reports and Publications (Box 587)
    - Service Classifications and Schedules (Box 587)
    - Movement for Economic Justice (Box 587)
    - New York State--General; Comparative Rates (Box 587)
    - New York State--Public Service Commission (Box 588)
    - New York Telephone Company:
      - General (Box 588)
      - Rate Increase:
        - Petitions and miscellaneous briefs (Box 588)
        - Public Service Commission (Box 588)
  - Subseries V.53: Welfare
    - Correspondence, 1969-1976 (Box 589)
    - Abzug--Notes, memoranda, statements, releases and activities (Box 590)
    - General, (2 Folders) (Box 590)
    - Aid to Families with Dependent Children and Unemployed Fathers (Box 590)
    - Center on Social Welfare Policy and Law (Box 590)
    - Child Support (Parent Locator) (Box 591)
    - Family Assistance Plan (Box 591)
    - Federalized Welfare (Box 591)
    - Health, Education and Welfare, U.S. Department of (Box 591)
    - Hearings, Statements and Testimony (Box 591)
    - Income Maintenance (Box 591)
    - Legislation:
      - 91st Congress (Box 591)
      - 92nd Congress:
        - General (Box 591)
        - HRI (Box 591)
      - 93rd Congress (Box 592)
      - 94th Congress:
        - General (Box 592)
        - HR 6430 (Box 592)
        - HR 9652--Correspondence, (3 Folders) (Box 592)
        - HR 9652 (Box 593)
          - Abzug--Notes, Memoranda, Statements, Releases (Box 593)
          - General (Box 593)
          - Citizens' Lobby (includes HR 1653) (Box 593)
          - Endorsements and Political Support (Box 593)
          - Puerto Rico (Box 593)
          - Statistics (Box 593)
        - Senate (Jacob K. Javits) (Box 593)
    - National Welfare Rights Organization (Box 593)
    - New York City: (Box 594)
      - General (Box 594)
      - Eligibility Studies--State Welfare Inspector General (Box 594)
      - Welfare Hotels (Box 594)
    - New York State--General; Legislation (Box 594)
    - Social Services, Department of--General; Projects and Programs (Box 595)
    - Rangel, Charles B. (Box 595)
    - Reports: (Box 596)
      - Joint Economic Committee, U.S. Congress (1 Folder, 17 volumes) (Box 596)
      - Miscellaneous, (2 Folders) (Box 596)
    - Wiseman, Frederick--Film (Box 597)
    - Women (Box 597)
    - Work Programs (Box 597)
    - Printed, (2 Folders) (Box 597)
  - Subseries V.54: Women
    - Correspondence, 1971-1975 (Box 598)
    - Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 599)
    - Abzug--Notes and Memoranda; Statements and Releases (Box 599)
    - General (Box 599)
    - Abortion: (Box 600)
      - Correspondence, 1971-1974 (Box 600)
      - Correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box 601)
      - Abzug--Memoranda and Notes; Statements and Releases General (Box 602)
      - Anti-Abortion Material (Box 602)
      - Catholic Church (Box 602)
      - Hearings and Testimony, 1974-1976 (Box 603)
      - Lawsuits, 1971 and miscellaneous (1 Folder, 1 volume) (Box 603)
      - Lawsuits, 1976 (Box 604)
      - Legislation, 1970 and miscellaneous (Box 604)
      - Legislation, 92nd and 93rd Congresses (Box 604)